<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    xmlns:ads="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:scrollbars="none"
        android:layout_weight="1"
        >




        <TableLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
            android:padding="5dp">

            <TableRow
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent">

                <ImageView
                    android:layout_width="150dp"
                    android:layout_height="150dp"
                    android:background="@drawable/director"
                    android:id="@+id/imageView" />

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
                    android:text="Dr.P.JAYARAMI REDDY"
                    android:id="@+id/textView2"
                    android:layout_column="1"
                    android:typeface="serif"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    android:textSize="30dp"
                    android:paddingTop="30dp" />

            </TableRow>

            <TableRow
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent">

            </TableRow>

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
                android:text="Dr. P. Jayarami Reddy, the Director of the College, is a rare combination of a popular   teacher, a famous researcher and an able administrator. To a great extent GPREC owes its   name and fame to this stalwart academician. Under his stewardship, discipline and   academic excellence have become the hallmarks of GPREC. He is one of the Triumvirate   of GPREC (1.Sri G.Pulla Reddy, the Founder Chairman 2. Sri R V Seshacharlu, the   Founder Treasure 3. Dr.P.Jaya Rami Reddy, the Director),  who have meticulously   prepared the frame work for the development of the institution and put a vibrant system   in place. He is the longest serving (30 years) Principal/Director of an engineering college   in Andhra Pradesh. It is not surprising that Dr.Jaya Rami Reddy’s name has become   synonymous with GPREC."
                android:id="@+id/textView96"
                android:textSize="30dp" />

            <TableRow
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent">

                <ImageView
                    android:layout_width="150dp"
                    android:layout_height="150dp"
                    android:background="@drawable/prince"
                    android:id="@+id/imageView2" />

                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
                    android:text="Dr.B.SRINIVASA REDDY"
                    android:id="@+id/textView3"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    android:typeface="serif"
                    android:textSize="30dp"
                    android:paddingTop="30dp" />
            </TableRow>

            <TableRow
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"></TableRow>

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
                android:text="Dr.Sreenivas Reddy, the Principal of the college, is known to be a hard task master and   represents the youthful exuberance of the institution.  Dr.B.Sreenivasa Reddy received his Ph.D   in Mechanical Engineering from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Hyderabad in   1998. After obtaining masters degree from Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani, he   joined the faculty of Mechanical Engineering of GPREC 1990 and has been serving the institute   since then. He headed the department of Mechanical Engineering as a professor from 2000 and   2007. He served the institute as Dean, Academics and Administration from 2006 to 2007. He   took over as the Principal of the college after Dr.Jaya Rami Reddy became the Director of the   college in 2007.  With his wide experience in teaching and administration, Prof. Sreenivasa   Reddy is striving hard to take the college to new heights.  Open to change and innovation,   with   ready willingness  to adopt and experiment new ideas, he tries out the best practices from around   and assimilates them, thus giving the institution a competitive edge."
                android:id="@+id/textView4"
                android:textSize="30dp" />

        </TableLayout>
    </ScrollView>
    <com.google.android.gms.ads.AdView
        android:id="@+id/ad_view"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        ads:adSize="BANNER"
        ads:adUnitId="@string/banner_ad_unit_id" />


</RelativeLayout>